Previously on
Two and a Half Men:
Hi.
LYNDSEY: I-I'm sorry.
I didn't catch your name.
This is Jeff.
Jeff Strongman.
In return for
51% of your company
I will back your project.
I will sell you
a minority share,
if you agree to work
as my product engineer.
You changed my code.
I made it better.
You're fired.
We're done. I don't
work with you anymore.
That's what
"you're fired" means.
So, this isn't
a bad idea anymore.
♪ Men. ♪
Oh. Hey, Jenny.
Oh. Do you have
plans for tonight?
You-You want to see a movie?
Uh, no. My girlfriend and I
are actually making one.
It's like The Hunger Games,
but we're not going
to be eating food.
ALAN: Oh. Hey, Walden.
Uh, want to go see a movie?
I got a buy one,
get one free coupon.
(laughing): No, I'm not falling
for that again.
And, besides, I can't.
I'm gonna go see Nicole...
Are you? Or are you gonna say
you're gonna go see Nicole?
And, we say,
that's a good idea.
But, then, you're gonna
talk about it a little more,
and decide, maybe
it's not a good idea.
And we say that's fine.
Whatever you want.
And then you come up to us
15 minutes later and say,
(deep voice):
"I'm gonna go see Nicole."
Maybe it's not a good idea.
Come on, just grow a pair.
Or strap on a pair from
my drawer and talk to her.
Or you could go
to a movie with me.
I'm gonna go see Nicole.
Hey, Berta,
want to go to the movies?
Sounds good. See you later.
♪ Men. ♪
Can I get
my free refill, please?
Sorry, sir.
That offer only applies
on the day of purchase.
I know. I, uh,
I purchased it today. So...
This is a Finding Nemo cup.
And you found him.
(laughs)
Uh, also there was a-a spider
in my, in my popcorn.
I had to throw
the whole thing away.
All right. All right. Well, just
tell your manager that, uh,
Alan Harper would like to speak
with him when he has a moment.
He knows me.
We all know you.
Jeff!
Oh! Oh, hey! (laughs)
Larry.
And, uh, uh...
I'm sorry, it's, um...
Lyndsey.
Right. Right. Of course.
I'm-I'm terrible with names.
(nervously laughs)
It's true. Sometimes he
can't even remember his own.
Well, I would never
forget it, Jeff Strongman.
Are you here alone?
Saturday night at the movies?
Alone? (laughs)
Hello, suicide hotline.
(laughs)
No. My date is, uh, um...
takin' a poop.
Is this date
something serious?
'Cause I was actually thinking,
there's a girl in my office,
Gwen, who would be
perfect for you.
Honey, I-I-I'm
pretty sure, Jeff is gay.
Nope. The only thing
straighter than me
is my boner when I
look at naked women.
(laughs)
Are you sure
you're not gay?
I'm sure.
Love the boobies.
You know, it might be fun,
we all go on a double date.
That would be great.
Would it?
Does that really
sound great, Jeff?
MANAGER:
Alan Harper?
I have a complimentary popcorn
and soda for Alan Harper?
Wow.
Free popcorn and soda.
Bet you wish
you were Alan Harper.
MANAGER:
Mr. Alan Harper?
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Men.
♪ Ooh.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x12 ♪
Baseball. Boobs. Boobs. Baseball
Original Air Date on January 9, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, guys.
Oh, my God.
I knew you'd come back.
I knew you were
not like my father.
Aw...
I missed you
invading my space.
Walden, hi.
What are you doing here?
Don't worry. I'm not
trying to get my job back.
I just wanted to see if
we could get dinner together.
Oh! Let me check my calendar.
What day were you thinking?
Yeah... I'm not so sure
that's a good idea.
Tuesday works for me.
I can skip Pilates.
Look, are... are you mad
about me kissing you?
No. I mean, yes!
I mean, did I think about it?
Sure... but-- ye--
I think about a lot of things.
You know, computers,
music, the weather.
Kissing me?
Yeah. No! No!
Stop it.
Okay. Wednesday,
I've got a thing,
but... uh...
you know what? I can move it.
Good-bye, Mom.
Look, even if there
were an attraction,
there are a hundred nerds
all around the world working on
thought-recognition technology,
and if I don't finish first,
I'm gonna lose the last
two years of my life.
All I heard was,
there is an attraction.
You like kissing me.
And... blah, blah, blah,
two years of my life.
Good-bye, Walden.
Okay. All I heard was,
you, me, pot, Jack in the Box,
blah, blah, blah,
best friends forever.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Oh, hey. How was the,
uh... movie?
Fantastic.
I went out by myself,
and came home with a date.
Wow. Normally you
go out with a date
and come home by yourself.
Where is she?
Oh, no-no.
It's a future date.
Future date?
Mm-hmm.
We talking like a, uh...
sex robot?
No, no. Lyndsey and Larry
are setting me up.
Although, if you do see
an ad for a sex robot,
save your money.
They just put lipstick
on a DustBuster.
Wa-Wa-Wa-Wait.
It's not the same DustBuster
you got me for Christmas?
Oh, no-no, of course not.
That-that would be, uh...
Oh, good God!
Wait a sec.
Your ex-girlfriend
and the guy she's with,
who she's cheating on with you,
is getting your alter ego,
Jeff Strongman,
a date with a girl
that they know?
Hang on, uh,
carry the whore. Yes.
So, uh, how'd it go with you?
Uh, well, I... went
to get a date with a girl,
got shot down, and wound up
with a date with a guy.
Been there.
(doorbell rings)
Ah, don't feel bad.
I've been shot down
more times than I can count,
and I'm still here.
BOTH:
We know.
Are you really that stupid?
Okay. You're talking to a guy
who stuck his penis in a vacuum.
What's wrong with you?
Wait, I keep a list
on the fridge.
Why in the world would you agree
to go on a double-date
with me and Larry?
Okay. You are just upset,
because you are gonna have to
watch me be with someone else,
the same way I have to
watch you be with Larry.
(Lyndsey sighs) This is just a taste
of your own medicine.
Jealous-in. Use as directed.
Side effects include
tears, sleepless nights,
and possible rage masturbation.
Number one, he's stupid.
Number two, smells like
mushroom soup.
Number three, he dates
that desperate chick who...
Number four...
Walden?
Hey, Bar-Bar.
Is Nicole there?
Uh... let me see...
(whispering):
I don't know what that means.
I do... I do not
understand what you're...
Sorry, Walden.
She's in a-a beating.
I think you meant meeting.
Did I?
(whispering): Did I?
Walden, hi.
Kinda busy. What's up?
I... have something for you.
Hang on.
(sighs)
I hate that she made me lie.
I-I love you.
That was weird.
But at, but at least,
at least it wasn't a lie.
You didn't want to
come to dinner.
, I brought dinner to you.
Oh, great. I am starving.
Oh, Barry.
It's, it's just for Nicole.
Is it because I lied to you?
No. It's because I like kissing
her just a little bit more.
This is really sweet.
But I have so much to do.
Come on...
My poor housekeeper
slaved all day
to make us
this delicious... note...
that says,
"I don't cook. Love, Berta."
Well-- I-I brought you
wine... and cheese...
and... no fricking corkscrew.
(nervously laughs)
I'll give you five minutes.
(laughs)
Well, appears the music
has stopped,
and I am left without a chair.
(remote clicks)
I only have six weeks to live.
Well, okay, that's not true,
but it is my birthday.
It, it really is my birthday.
Look, Walden,
just because
I agreed to do this,
I don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
(British accent):
Well, it's too late.
Once the lady accepts
the man's cheese,
they must marry.
(British accent): But I am
betrothed to a goatherd.
Is that a smile?
Are you actually having fun?
(laughs) Uh... yes, but I really
have to get back to work.
Let me help you.
We tried that.
BARRY (over speaker):
Give him a chance...
Barry, what did we talk about?
Digital boundaries.
Am I the only one
feeling a connection here?
Of course not.
But, because of that,
you're gonna be a distraction.
Well, I-I promise
to wear a conservative top.
And to tape down
all my fun parts.
Uh... All right.
I will let you help.
But, until we're done,
it has to be all work
and no play.
Deal. But I'm--
you're gonna have to let me
tape down your fun parts.
♪ Men. ♪
You got this? You ready?
(laughs)
Mm-hmm.
LARRY & ALAN:
One...
two...
three...
four...
five... cherries...!
♪ Ta-da!
(laughs)
Wow!
Wow. You did that with your tongue?
Mm-hmm.
But I-- trust me
when I tell you,
uh, that I am giving you
a standing ovation.
(laughs)
Trust me when I tell you,
I have an erection.
Isn't she great?
Yeah, she's great.
So, uh... you work with Larry?
Do you manage musicians too?
No. I'm in talent relations.
Basically, my job is to make
sure everyone's happy.
Well, job well done tonight.
I-I can't remember the last time
I had so much fun on a date.
(laughs)
Maybe the problem's you, Jeff.
I don't think so.
I think you're yummy.
Well, uh... I have been
using a coconut body butter.
GWEN: Oh.
Didn't I tell you
these two would hit it off?
Next stop, couples trip
to wine country.
Can't wear a thong bikini
in wine country.
Cabo, it is.
You should wear
a thong, sweetie.
Another great idea.
Oh... I just got invited to a
party in the hills tonight.
You guys want to go?
Yes! No!
Yes!
Come on,
aren't you having fun?
Look, if you don't want to go,
I can give the guys
a ride to the party.
Jeff in the front...
Larry in the rear...
It'll be tight but,
we can make it work.
Aw...
I don't think
it'd be that tight.
Oh, I'm going to the party.
Uh, uh, let's just
give it a minute to...
(Lyndsey sighs)
Crowd's still on its feet.
♪ Men. ♪
Um...
Wow. Uh, looks
like we're overdressed.
I can fix that.
Gwen!
Yeah, come on.
It's a swingers' party.
All right. Let's do this thing.
♪ Men. ♪
(thunder crashing)
(sighs) It's like
a hundred degrees in here.
Yeah, right?
I've got frozen
peas in my crotch.
What?
I got a bag of frozen peas,
and I put 'em down my pants.
It's delightful.
Okay. You know what?
This is ridiculous.
We gotta be able to
fix this radiator.
I've got a call in,
they're coming out tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Come on!
We got three geniuses here.
Yeah, and one of 'em
has frozen peas
in his underwear.
What underwear?
Still, we can make this work.
Yeah. I mean, it's--
clearly the-the heat is...
emanating from, uh...
from this device.
We just, we just
need to... reboot it.
You say the guy's
coming out tomorrow?
Yes, geniuses.
Now, will you
help me figure out
why this algorithm
isn't working?
Maybe it's on a Java break.
(Barry laughs)
Did you get it?
Like java and Java...?
That joke killed
at MIT open mic night.
What do you got?
You-- oh... this
pointer is undefined.
Oh. Right. Of course.
So, uh... guess you
got it from here.
What are we waiting for?
I mean, let's just do this.
Really?
What about Barry?
He can film it.
What?
I mean, we're gonna want to
watch it again and again.
You know, maybe even
put it on the Internet.
This is a pleasant surprise.
(laughs)
Here, let's test it.
Oh... yeah, right, the device.
Mm-hmm.
That's exactly what
we were talking about.
Good. Now put that on.
(whispering):
And stop thinking about sex.
Well, it's harder than it looks.
Well, it's a good thing
you taped it down.
Now...
the first thing you think
will be the first human thought
recognized by a computer.
It's not even
reading the device.
Now, you know what?
I think I know what it is.
If it's any consolation,
I thought she was
talking about sex, too.
P.S. Just throwing
this out there:
totally up for filming.
♪ Men. ♪
Uh, uh-uh, let me
ask you something.
Um... uh, how do I put this?
Um... i-i-is there a "grow room"
before the "show room"?
There's a blow room.
How 'bout this?
You said you wanted to
spice things up.
This seems pretty spicy.
And it sure beats the hell
out of couples' therapy, huh, Jeff?
Uh, y-you know,
if Lyndsey is uncomfortable,
why don't you guys take off?
Some people can't handle
seeing their partner
with someone else.
You know what? I'm good.
Besides, I've always
wanted to sleep with Jeff.
Wait. What?
You heard me.
Let's do this thing.
I'm gonna go get us
some drinks.
I'll come with you.
You're gonna be
hearing that a lot tonight.
Isn't this great, Jeff?
I get to bang Gwen,
and you get to bang Lyndsey.
Yeah, that's one way to go.
Um... Or I-I could
have sex with Gwen,
and you could do
whatever the hell you want.
(laughs) Come on,
you're telling me
when you're nailing someone,
you never imagined
it was Lyndsey?
Never once.
Well, you got
the green light, buddy.
This is so exciting.
I haven't had sex with
somebody new in a long time.
Yeah, me neither.
♪ Men. ♪
You know...
Okay, there's a reason
I didn't respond
the first time you said it.
Walden?
I... need... it.
Walden.
I need it.
What?
The file you were
supposed to send me.
I need it.
Oh... uh, yeah, right.
The file. Sorry.
Is... this...
what... you... want...?
Nicole.
Is this what you wanted?
Huh?
The file. It's right here.
Oh. Right. Yeah.
Let me just...
put it in.
Oh, wow...
This really sucks.
We have so much work to do,
and all I can think about
is you and me, and oh, wow.
Gotta stop
thinking about sex.
How are we gonna do that?
BARRY:
Oh, yeah.
That's...
what... daddy... likes...
And that did it.
(clears throat)
♪ Men. ♪
Is this seat taken?
Oh.
Very funny.
Okay, good news, bad news.
Bad news, Larry's with Gwen.
Yeah. Not a big surprise.
She's got boobs that could
save your life
in the event
of a water landing.
But the good news is,
guess who's got two thumbs,
and is banging you tonight.
This guy...!
Jeff Probst?!
You ready, babe?
Oh, yeah.
Wait! What the hell?
I told you I wanted
to sleep with Jeff.
But I'm Jeff.
No, you're Alan.
So, what do you say,
blow room first?
If you told Larry
you were gay,
none of this
would have happened.
(sighs)
Wait. That guy's not gay?
♪ Men. ♪
(moans)
Thanks again for
the birthday pudding, you guys.
I love pudding.
It's even fun to say.
Pu-dding.
I'm putting pudding in my mouth.
(laughs hysterically)
(laughing): Oh, my God.
That's funny.
(Barry continues laughing)
Looks like the
birthday weed is kicking in.
Putting pudding.
Okay. Now I'm gonna
switch it up,
and see if you can
tell the difference.
Pudding putting.
Oh, my God.
I got it.
Did you?
The-The-The function.
It's recursive.
It keeps getting stuck
in the subroutine.
This is, this is it.
You sure?
Yeah. No, check it out.
This is history.
This is like
Alexander Graham Bell saying,
"Watson, come here."
This is Neil Armstrong saying,
"One small step for man."
This is Walden Schmidt saying...
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Pudding.
Aw, damn it, Barry!
You put pudding in my head!
Putting pudding.
Or, putting pudding.
I was gonna say,
"The future is now."
"The future is now"?
What is this,
the 1912 World's Fair?
Excuse me, guys.
What?
I think the computer
just read his thoughts.
We did it!
Oh, my God.
It worked.
(screaming)
It worked!
(laughing, yelling)
Yes!
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Someone's not wearing a bra.
What?!
I...
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Stop thinking about sex.
Baseball. Boobs. Boobs.
Baseball. Baseball.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
This was a great idea, Walden.
It was.
You're so beautiful.
Thank you.
And you're so handsome.
I am so turned on, Nicole.
So am I.
Uh-oh. Baseball.
Baseball. Baseball.
Oh, crap.
Now I want pudding.
♪ Men. ♪
This is gym class
all over again.
Last man picked
and I have an unwanted boner.
I wouldn't say it's unwanted.
Oh. Hello.
Well, looks like
it's just you and me.
Yeah... Jeff Probst
stole my girlfriend.
Bastard.
(laughs)
He's my grandson.
Wow! Uh, I-I-I can't believe
he'd bring his grandmother
to a party like this.
(chuckling): He can't bring me
to my own party.
Wait, but this is your house?
That's right.
What do you say?
You want to go road test
this new hip?
All right. Why not?
Well, we'll start
in the grow room. Come on.
Oh, this is a beautiful house.
Do you have a guest room?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man